Urban League of Northeastern New York; Records apap008
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- National Urban League Files, 1966-1987; 3; 4 cubic ft.
  - Guidelines for Assessment (Dues), 1969 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 59)
  - Guidelines for Certification of Executive Directors, 1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 60)
  - Guild Information, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 61)
  - Guidelines for Regional Assemblies, 1982 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 62)
  - Harold R. Sims-Acting Executive Director, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 63)
  - Housing and Urban Development Act of 1966 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 64)
  - Housing Department Publications, 1971-1975 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 1)
  - Housing Research Conference, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 2)
  - How To Organize An Urban League, 1967 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 3)
  - Income Maintenance Policy, 1968-1970 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 4)
  - Institutional Change Workshop Report, 1969 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 5)
  - Interracial Colloquy, 1970 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 6)
  - Labor Affairs Program, 1976 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 7)
  - Labor Education Advancement, 1970-1974 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 8)
  - Law and Consumer Affairs, 1971 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1969 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 10)
  - Legislative Memorandum, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 11)
  - Local Affiliates, 1984 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 12)
  - Lewis Harris Survey, 1970 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 13)
  - Memorandum, 1968-1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 14)
  - Management Training, 1975 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 15)
  - Manual for Affiliates, 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 16)
  - Marshall Plan, 1967 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 17)
  - Management Training and Development Center, 1978 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 18)
  - Manpower Economic Development and Labor Affairs Council, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 19)
  - Manual on Direct cost Recovery, 1979 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 20)
  - Manual for Affiliates, 1972-1974 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 21)
  - Mid-Winter Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 22)
  - National Board of Trustees, 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 23)
  - National Conference, Undated (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 24)
  - National Conference, 1963 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 25)
  - National Conference, 1969 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 26)
  - National Conference, 1973 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 27)
  - National Advertising Campaign, 1984 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 28)
  - National Priorities Report, 1985 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 29)
  - News clippings, 1967-1969 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 30)
  - Newsletter, 1968-1975 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 31)
  - News from National Urban League, 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 32)
  - News from National Urban League, 1973 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 33)
  - News from National Urban League, 1974 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 34)
  - News from National Urban League, 1979 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 35)
  - News from National Urban League, 1980 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 36)
  - News from National Urban League, 1982 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 37)
  - News from National Urban League, 1984 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 38)
  - News from National Urban League, 1986 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 39)
  - News Releases, 1969 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 40)
  - News Releases, 1970 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 41)
  - News Releases, 1971 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 42)
  - News Releases, 1984 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 43)
  - News Releases, 1985 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 44)
  - News Releases, 1986 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 45)
  - New Thrust for Urban League Movement, 1968 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 46)
  - New Thrust for Urban League Movement, 1969 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 47)
  - New Thrust for Urban League Movement, 1971 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 48)
  - New York State Council of Urban League Executives, 1971-1974 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 49)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 50)
  - Notices, 1969-1971 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 51)
  - "Not the Leader, But the Leadership", 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 52)
  - Office of General Counsel, 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 53)
  - On-the-Job Training Program, 1968-1970 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 54)
  - Operation Breakthrough, 1970 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 55)
  - Partisan Political Activity, 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 56)
  - Partnerships, 1983 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 57)
  - Personnel Department, 1972 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 58)
  - Personnel Information Bulletin, 1969-1971 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 59)
  - Planning Session, 1974 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 60)
  - Poor People's March, 1968 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 61)
  - Presentation to Regional Assemblies, 1985 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 62)
  - President Council, 1974 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 63)
  - President's Commission on Civil Disorders, 1968 (Box 3 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 64)
  - Priority Setting, Planning and Review Process, 1983 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 1)
  - President's Report, 1984 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 2)
  - Proceedings of Health and Social Welfare Workshop, 1975 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 3)
  - Progress Report, 1969-1973 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 4)
  - Project E.N.A.B.L.E., 1967-1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1967 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 6)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1982 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 7)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1983 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 8)
  - Records Retention Program, 1972 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 9)
  - Regional Offices, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 10)
  - Rent Supplement Program, 1966 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 11)
  - Research Department, 1969 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 12)
  - Retirement Income Program, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 13)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1971-1973 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 14)
  - San Francisco Urban League, 1970-1974 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 15)
  - Search Committee, 1971 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 16)
  - The Secretariat, 1967 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 17)
  - The Secretariat, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 18)
  - The Secretariat, 1969 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 19)
  - School Decentralization, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 20)
  - Social Welfare, 1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 21)
  - Social Welfare, 1975 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 22)
  - Speaker's Bureau, 1984 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 23)
  - Staff Quarterly, 1980 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 24)
  - Statement's By Vernon Jordan, Jr., 1971-1973 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 25)
  - Statements of Concern, 1969 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 26)
  - Staff Appointments, 1974 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 27)
  - Staff Changes, 1968-1972 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 28)
  - Survival Fund, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 29)
  - Tarrytown Conference and Development of the NUL Planning Unit, 1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 30)
  - To Be Equal, 1974 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 31)
  - To Be Equal, 1975 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 32)
  - To Be Equal, 1976 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 33)
  - Training Seminar Program, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 34)
  - Transportation Needs of Handicapped and Elderly, 1972 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 35)
  - United Funds, 1971 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 36)
  - United Fund National Corporation Cultivation Project, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 37)
  - United Way, 1974 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 38)
  - United Way Campaign, 1985 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 39)
  - United Way Funding, 1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 40)
  - Urban League Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 41)
  - Urban League Business--An Approach to Action, 1966 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 42)
  - Urban League Manifesto, 1969 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 43)
  - Urban League Sunday, 1986 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 44)
  - Urban League Volunteer Groups, 1984 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 45)
  - United States Congress, 1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 46)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 47)
  - Voter Registration Procedure, 1971-1974 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 48)
  - Vernon Jordan, Jr. -- Biographical Sketch, 1972 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 49)
  - Vernon Jordan, Jr. -- Public Statements, 1974-1976 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 50)
  - Wage Supplement Campaign, 1969 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 51)
  - Washington Bureau Elections, 1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 52)
  - Washington Bureau Newsletters, 1967-1972 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 53)
  - Washington Operations, Undated (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 54)
  - Washington Operations, 1982 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 55)
  - Washington Operations, 1983 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 56)
  - Washington Operations, 1984 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 57)
  - Washington Operations, 1988 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 58)
  - Washington Operations-Congressional Digest, 1988 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 59)
  - Which Way America, 1971; 1974 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 60)
  - White House Conference on Handicapped Individuals, 1976 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 61)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Speeches, 1967 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 62)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Speeches, 1968 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 63)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Speeches, 1969 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 64)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Speeches, 1970 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 65)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Speeches, 1971 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 66)
  - Youth Activities, 1968-1971 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 67)
  - Youth Employment and Training Programs, 1984 (Box 4 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 68)
- Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program, 1984-1987; 4; 0.5 cubic ft.
  The series contains records of the AVE program. The program was funded through a grant provided by the New York State Department of Education. The goal of the program was to develop life and career skills in "youth-at-risk" of not completing their education. The participants were engaged in a series of temporary placements to explore career options and further clarify their goals.
  Arranged alphabetically and chronologically there under.
  - Academic Credit Handbook, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 1)
  - AVE Handbook, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 2)
  - Grant Applications, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 3)
  - Health Careers Opportunity Program-Grant Applications, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 4)
  - Mid-Winter Conference, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 5)
  - A Program Model for Urban League Math and Science Program, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 6)
  - Survey of Urban League Affiliates on Public School Programs for Academically Gifted Minorities, Undated (Box 1 (4-Adolescent Vocational Exploration Program), Folder 7)